Ben: Hey!
What are you doing?
Izzy: What’s wrong with you?
Ben: Look, I made a mistake, OK?
Izzy: I’m so embarrassed.
Couldn’t you see it was a work photo?
Ben: I said I’m sorry, OK!
But it’s always a work ‘something’ with you these days.
Is that all you think about?
Your wonderful job?
Izzy: What?
Are you annoyed that I’m successful?
Ben: No, of course not.
I’m very proud of you, but…
but there’s never any time for us.
And what’s going on with Max?
Izzy: Max?
Oh, come on, Ben.
Now you are acting like a child.
Max is my boss.
I work with him.
I work for him.
There’s nothing going on…Do you really think I would do that to you?
Ben: I don’t know.
I feel like I don’t know who you are anymore.
Izzy: That’s not fair.
I’m me.
I’m Izzy.
If you don’t like who I am, then I…
Ben: Then what?
Izzy: I can’t have this conversation with you right now.
Ben: I’m not following you, if that’s what you want.